[Music]
okay this is the entry right yes okay
[Applause]
[Music]
companies like infosis limited with
Fidelity Investments and then I have
been an independent consultant for a lot
of different organizations in the field
of Learning and Development that's a
little bit about me happy to be here
this is the last patch for IC lombar the
Synergy uh session so I've had you know
interacted with a lot of people B my
these regions mostly for conducting this
particular workshop and looking forward
uh to finishing this particular uh
session today with you know with so that
you all can go back and take all the
learnings and apply all the learnings
also so along with me today we have uh
from ICC Al Luma Mr
ammed our service center which is in
Mumbai uh very glad to you know be part
of this session which is the last
session uh in Bangalore uh look forward
for lot of interaction and learning from
all of you as well yeah thanks thank you
sir just one request you know guys you
just keep your phone back down but
clearly a thought in itself is not
enough we as an entity are more known
for what we execute rather than what we
think the moment there's a convergence
between thought and if it's executed
well we can see what magic we can create
what got started in a mere line of one
as one team has exploded into multiple
Contours as a team we have done multiple
initiatives thanks to each one of you
participating in full measure philosophy
these are the behaviors that go into it
so next what we will do
is for the next 3 minutes we are going
to on your table next 3 minutes on your
table have a discussion around if you
have
[Music]
right so
now we've been talking about can
apologize when I make a
mistake I don't let my ego moment to
play here I do that
I'm in
[Music]
my I